in this lecture we will use inkscape to
在这堂课中，我们将使用Inkscape
automatically vectorize a bitmap logo
自动矢量化位图徽标
I will use Bing image Creator to get
我将使用Bing图像创建器来获得
some ideas for a logo
关于徽标的一些想法
Bing image Creator is a free service and
Bing Image Creator是一项免费服务，
you can type what kind of logo you want
您可以键入您想要的徽标
I typed logo coffee shop flat design
我打出了咖啡厅平面设计的标志
minimalistic three colors and on a white
简约的三种颜色和一种白色
background
背景
I created several examples and
我创建了几个例子，
downloaded a logo I liked
下载了我喜欢的徽标
in inkscape I go to file import
在Inkscape中，我转到文件导入
I open the coffee shop logo
我打开咖啡店的标志
I will crop the logo using the rectangle
我将使用矩形裁剪徽标
tool
工具
I drag over the logo press the space bar
我拖过徽标，按下空格键
and position the rectangle
并将矩形放置在
I shift-click on the image
我按住Shift键并单击图像
I right click and choose set clip
我右击并选择Set Clip
I right click again and choose crop
我再次右击并选择裁剪
image to clip I right click a third time
第三次右击要剪辑的图像
and choose Trace bitmap
并选择轨迹位图
in the last lecture we used single scan
在上一节课中，我们使用了单次扫描
to create a brush
创建笔刷
now we have a color image so I click on
现在我们有了一张彩色图像，所以我点击
the multi-color tab
多色标签
for detection mode I choose colors scans
对于检测模式，我选择彩色扫描
means the amount of paths that will be
表示将被
created which is by default on 8.
已创建，默认情况下为8。
let's see if I can get fewer paths if I
让我们看看我是否能得到更少的路径
reduce scans I see that I can bring the
减少扫描我看到我可以把
amount of paths down to six
路径数量降至六条
I also want inkscape to remove the white
我还想让Inkscape去掉白色
background
背景
let's see what happens if I click on
让我们看看如果我点击
apply
应用
when I zoom in I see some speckles
当我放大时，我看到一些斑点
this means inkscape made a very detailed
这意味着Inkscape制作了一个非常详细的
scan
扫描
so let's try again
所以让我们再试一次
when I hold my mouse above Speckles I
当我把鼠标举到斑点上方时，我
read that by increasing it small spots
通过增加小斑点来阅读它
will be ignored
将被忽略
so I increase the Speckles value
所以我增加了斑点的值
I will also select stack which attempts
我还将选择尝试的堆栈
to reduce gaps
缩小差距
I click on apply now let's optimize the
我点击Apply Now让我们优化
scan in my layers I see I have a group
扫描我的层，我看到我有一个组
of paths I hold alt to look at the
我按住Alt键来查看
layers
层层
I zoom in on the most right element
我放大最右边的元素
we see the path is not smooth
我们看到道路并不平坦
so I go to path simplify I see that the
所以我转到路径简化，我看到
shortcut is Ctrl l
快捷键是Ctrl键L
this already looks better
这个看起来已经更好了
let's have a look at the nodes I select
让我们来看看我选择的节点
the node tool
节点工具
I think I can reduce the amount of nodes
我想我可以减少节点数
even more so I press Ctrl l now I can
更重要的是，我现在可以按下Ctrl键L
easily adjust the shape when needed I
根据需要轻松调整形状
select the middle element I press Ctrl L
选择中间元素我按Ctrl键L
three times when I click on the left
当我点击左侧三次时
element I see I have a compound path
元素，我看到我有一条复合路径
I prefer to work with individual
我更喜欢与个人合作
elements so I go to path split path
元素，因此我转到路径拆分路径
in my layers I see I have now two
在我的层次中，我看到我现在有两个
separate paths with the same color I
将具有相同颜色的路径分开
select the left element
选择左侧元素
I press Ctrl l two times
我按了两次Ctrl键L
then I select the black outline and go
然后我选择黑色轮廓，然后开始
to path split path I select the handle
要为拆分路径设置路径，请选择控制柄
I press Ctrl L several times now I
现在我按了几次Ctrl键L
select the cup outline
选择杯子轮廓
I see it get an undesired effect in the
我看到它得到了一个不受欢迎的效果
corner when I press Ctrl l
当我按下Ctrl键时角点L
so I press Ctrl set let's see what
所以我按下Ctrl Set，让我们看看
happens when I delete individual
当我删除个人时发生
Superfluous nodes
多余的节点
I remove some nodes at the right each
我删除了每个右侧的一些节点
time I remove a node inkscape will
我删除节点Inkscape时将
restore the curve as good as it can
尽可能地恢复曲线
finally let's look at the inside of the
最后，让我们看看它的内部
cup I select the green element and press
杯我选择绿色元素并按下
Ctrl l two times
Ctrl L两次
because I will expand the shape to
因为我要将该形状扩展为
remove gaps I will delete all
删除空白我将删除所有
Superfluous nodes
多余的节点
now I only have to drag three nodes to
现在，我只需将三个节点拖到
remove any gaps
消除所有缝隙
the shape above is below the green shape
上面的形状在绿色形状的下面
here I will press Ctrl L several times
这里我会按几次Ctrl键L
to remove as much nodes as possible to
要删除尽可能多的节点，以
remove all gaps I increase its size
移除所有间隙我增加它的大小
holding shift plus control
按住Shift+控制
I have now traced the logo and I
我现在已经追踪到了徽标，我
optimize the paths to a minimum amount
将路径优化到最小数量
of nodes so I can easily adjust the
这样我就可以轻松地调整
shapes if needed
形状(如果需要)